<resources>
    <string name="write_secure_settings_permission" translatable="false">android.permission.WRITE_SECURE_SETTINGS</string>
    <string name="adb_command" translatable="false">adb shell pm grant %1s %2s</string>

    <string name="permission_missing">Permission missing!</string>
    <string name="grant_permission_adb">Please give \"write secure settings\" permission running the following ADB command \"%1s\" and force close the app, for further instructions please visit the apps wiki</string>
    <string name="usage_permission_missing">Usage stats permission missing, please grant it in the following screen</string>
    <string name="app_info_1">Monochromatic is an app to facilitate phone usage at night, by enabling the built in monochrome feature in Android 5 or later</string>
    <string name="app_info_2">As this changes a system setting uninstalling this app wont revert it, to do that either disable the app before uninstalling or change back to color mode in the developer settings</string>
    <string name="app_info_3">By default Monochromatic is set to always on, you can change when grey scale is enabled in the settings, under the menu in the top right!</string>

    <string name="app_info_about">Unlike other night screen apps, this doesn\'t create an overlay, enabling monochrome for all screens and views, and does not interfere with android secure actions such as installing apps</string>
    <string name="notification_dismiss_notice">Starting from android 8 apps are required to show a notification to be able to run in the background, the notification can be hidden by holding down on it and toggling the switch that appears</string>
    <string name="service_enabled">Monochromatic enabled</string>
    <string name="service_disabled">Monochromatic disabled</string>
    <string name="by_richyhbm">By RichyHBM</string>
    <string name="toggle">Monochrome</string>

    <string name="wiki">Wiki</string>
    <string name="disable">Disable</string>
    <string name="disable_for_screen">Screen</string>
    <string name="disable_for_session">Session</string>
    <string name="share_command">Share Command</string>
    <string name="toggle_greyscale">Toggle Greyscale</string>
    <string name="toggling_please_wait">Toggling, please wait!</string>
    <string name="force_color">Force color</string>
    <string name="whitelist">Whitelist</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
</resources>
